Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Chronological Files, 1958-2003
  - Sub-Series I: Correspondence, Minutes and Other Material affiliated with Gordon Moore, 1958-2003
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Project re: American Industry at Crossroads - Correspondence, Outline, Essay/Article re: Intel Memories and the Microprocessor [Originally in Box 70, Folder 7], November 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University, School of Business, Jack McDonald’s Class - Presentation Outline, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 71, Folder 2], November 1994 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Supercomputing Meeting, Washington - Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 71, Folder 3], November 1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Santa Clara University Technology Forecast re: Technology Trends: Challenges Facing the Silicon Valley Microelectronics Industry - Correspondence, Brochures, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Outline re: Can We Keep the Silicon in Silicon Valley [Originally in Box 71, Folder 5], November 1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Oversized Poster Representation of Pentium Pro (P6) Microprocessor [Originally in Box 71, Folder 7], December 1994 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Caltech Associates Presentation Outline re: My Vision for Caltech [Originally in Box 71, Folder 9], January 1995 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Profit and Loss Review, Plan 1999 - Presentation Slides, 1998 Plan Reference Book, Business Indicators, Financial Results, Cyrix case 1991, Microsoft packet [Originally in Box 71, Folder 12], 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Profit and Loss Review, Plan 1999 - Presentation Slides re: Technology and Manufacturing Group, Communications Group, Mobile/Handheld Products Group, Desktop Products Group, Agenda, Strategic Review, Correspondence (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 72, Folder 1], 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - SPIE International Society for Optical Engineering Microlithography Symposium - Correspondence, Transcript, Presentation Slides re: Lithography and Future of Moore’s Law, Agenda, Newsletter, Program [Originally in Box 72, Folder 3], February 1995 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Palo Alto Churchill Club Conference - Transcript re: Silicon Valley Business [Originally in Box 73, Folder 1], May 1995 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - HOT Chips VII (A Symposium on High-Performance Chips), Stanford University - Presentation Slides re: Nanometers and Gigabucks, Correspondence, Map, Agenda [Originally in Box 73, Folder 4], August 1995 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Nikkei Business Publications Grand Opening - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 73, Folder 5], September 1995 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Intel Corp. Worldwide Treasury Conference - Presentation Slides re: Nanometers and Gigabucks, Correspondence, Agenda [Originally in Box 73, Folder 7], October 1995 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University, School of Business, Jack McDonald’s Class - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 73, Folder 10], November 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Agenda, Memo, Securities and Exchange Commission Form S-8, 401(k) Savings Plan, Presentation Slides, Minutes [Originally in Box 74, Folder 1], November 1995 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Alliance to Revitalize California Breakfast re: Fundraising - Agenda, Correspondence [Originally in Box 74, Folder 4], January 1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - University Video Communications Distinguished Lecture on Moore’s Law - Correspondence, Pamphlet, Presentation Slides re: Nanometers and Gigabucks [Originally in Box 74, Folder 5], January 1996 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Senator Dianne Feinstein Meeting re: Budget Deficit, Tax Issues, Legal Immigration, TEAM Act, Encryption, Trade - Correspondence, San Diego State University Defense Conversion Center Resume Book, Pamphlets re: Federal Budget Deficit [Originally in Box 74, Folder 7], February 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Healthcare Information and Management Systems Society (HIMSS) Video - Presentation Slides re: Healthcare and Microprocessors, Video Clip Transcripts [Originally in Box 75, Folder 1], March 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Business School Global Alumni Conference re: The Information Revolution - Agenda, Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 75, Folder 2], March 1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - The Seventh Roundtable in Multimedia re: Models for the Next Millennium - Program, Correspondence [Originally in Box 75, Folder 3], 1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Business School Alumni Association Meeting – Presentation Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 75, Folder 6], April 1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Computerworld Smithsonian Monticello Memoirs Program, University of Virginia - Presentation Outline, Notes, Correspondence, Program, Photograph Contact Sheet [Originally in Box 75, Folder 7], April 1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. New York Analyst Meeting - Agenda, Booklet, Correspondence, Presentation Speech [Originally in Box 76, Folder 2], May 1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - MIT Research Laboratory of Electronics (RLE) Article on Robert Noyce - Correspondence, Article, RLE Currents, Vol. 8 No. 1 [Originally in Box 76, Folder 4], July 1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Microdesign Resources Annual Microprocessor Forum - Presentation Slides re: Microprocessors: Past, Present and Future, Programs, Article re: The Future of the Microprocessors by Albert Yu, Presentation Outline, Pamphlet re: Die Photo Gallery (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 76, Folder 7], October 1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Microdesign Resources Annual Microprocessor Forum Conference Materials - Presentation Slides, Agenda (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 77, Folder 1], October 1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Press Coverage in Japan - Correspondence, Articles, Presentation Outlines, Presentation Slides re: Microprocessor at 25 years, Booklet, Interview Translations, Agendas [Originally in Box 77, Folder 2], November 1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - International Electron Devices Meeting Conference - Program, Presentation Slides, Presentation Outline re: Silicon Device Fabrication Technology Revisited, Correspondence [Originally in Box 78, Folder 2], December 1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. Documents Removed re: Gerhard H. Parker, General Manager of the Technology and Manufacturing Group, re: Techsearch versus Intel Corp, Small Desktop (SDT) and CID [Originally in Box 78, Folder 3], 1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - University of Cambridge Cavendish Laboratory - Electron Centennial Meeting- Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Development of Microelectronics Industry, Agenda, Brochures, Booklet, Press Release re: New Pentium Processor PC Given to Stephen Hawking, Articles, Newsletter, Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 78, Folder 7], March 1997 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - The Electrochemical Society Inc. Meeting, Montreal - Correspondence, Program, Presentation Slides re: Fifty Years of Semiconductor Technology, Presentation Outline, Brochure, Interface Magazine, Vol. 6, No. 1, Vol. 5, No. 1-3 (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 79, Folder 3], May 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Electrochemical Society Inc. Meeting, Montreal - Interface Magazine, Vol. 6, No. 1, Vol. 5, No. 1-3 (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 79, Folder 4], May 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. New York Analyst Meeting - News Releases, Agenda, Booklet, Correspondence, Intel Technology Series - Agendas re: The Future of Business Computing: The Visual Connected PC [Originally in Box 80, Folder 1], June 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ECO Summit, Santa Clara - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 80, Folder 2], June 1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Intel Developer Forum - Program, Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: The Technology that ate the Industry [Originally in Box 80, Folder 3], September 1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Intel Corp. Press Conference re: EUV (Extreme-Ultraviolet) Lithography Program - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 80, Folder 4], September 1997 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Semiconductor Research Corp. Graduate Fellowship Program Annual Conference - Agenda, Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Fifty Years of Semiconductor Technology [Originally in Box 80, Folder 5], September 1997 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Grinnell College Robert Noyce Science Center Dedication – Program, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings [Originally in Box 80, Folder 6], September 1997 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - ISSM International Symposium on Semiconductor Manufacturing Conference - Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Program, Presentation Slides re: Manufacturing: The Bridge to Next Millennium [Originally in Box 80, Folder 7], October 1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University, School of Business, Jack McDonald’s Class - Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 80, Folder 8], October 1997 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Notes, Presentation Slides re: Research at Intel [Originally in Box 80, Folder 9], October 1997 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Treasury Conference - Presentation Slides and Outline re: Technology that Drives the Industry [Originally in Box 80, Folder 10], October 1997 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Electronic Engineering Times 25th Anniversary - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 80, Folder 11], November 1997 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Lucent Technologies/Bell Labs Seminar re: 50th Anniversary of the Invention of the Transistor - Notes, Brochure, Correspondence, Agenda, Program, Bell Labs Newsletter, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 80, Folder 12], November 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Materials Symposium - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 80, Folder 13], March 1998 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Museum of American Heritage Event: “Toys and Moore” - Agenda, Presentation Outline re: Introduction of Silicon into Silicon Valley [Originally in Box 80, Folder 15], June 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - International Federation for Information Processing World Computer Congress, Vienna, Austria - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Computing Past, Present, and Future, Program, Correspondence, Agenda, Demonstration Scripts [Originally in Box 80, Folder 16], August 1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Riverside High School Mathematics and Science Summer Institute - Program, Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Role of Technology in Past and New Millennium, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 81, Folder 1], August 1998 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Computer History Museum Fellow Award - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 81, Folder 3], November 1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University, School of Business, Jack McDonald’s Class - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 81, Folder 4], November 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Oregon Graduate Institute, Gordon and Betty Moore Endowed Chair of Electrical and Computing Engineering - Presentation Outline, Notes [Originally in Box 81, Folder 5], undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. ESM Security Reading List Materials [Originally Box 81, Folder 6] [Restricted until 2019], February 1999 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - American Physical Society Centennial Meeting - Presentation Outline (Used at Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory), Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Birth of Integrated Circuit, Program [Originally in Box 81, Folder 7], March 1999 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - American Physical Society Centennial Meeting - Presentation Outline (Used at Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory), Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Birth of Integrated Circuit, Program [removed from Box 32 Folder 9] [Restricted until 2019] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 7], March 1999 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides re: The History of the Integrated Circuit [Restricted until 2019] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 9], May 1999 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Churchill Club and Computer History Museum Center Program - Correspondence, Presentation Outline (Used at APS), Presentation Slides re: Birth of Integrated Circuit [Restricted until 2019] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 10], October 1999 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - WDC Conference - Presentation Outline, Overhead Transparencies re: SEMATECH, Presentation Slides re: External Programs Overview by Mike Ryan [Restricted until 2020] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 11], October 2000 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Chemical Heritage Foundation, Donald Othmer Award - Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Presentation Slides [Restricted until 2021] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 12], April 2001 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - PCAST (President’s Council of Advisors on Science and Technology) Questionnaire - Correspondence [Restricted until 2021] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 14], August 2001 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Caltech Seminar Day - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Semiconductor Revolution, Badge, Program, Correspondence, Stickers [Originally in Box 81, Folder 15], May 2002 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Caltech Seminar Day - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Semiconductor Revolution, Badge, Program, Correspondence, Stickers [Restricted until 2022] [Removed from Box 32 Folder 10] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 15], May 2002 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association, San Jose - Presentation Slides re: Semiconductor Revolution, Presentation Outline [Restricted until 2002] [Originally in Box 81, Folder 16], November 2002 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series II: Outgoing Business Correspondence from Gordon Moore, 1984-2003
    This subseries contains outgoing business correspondence from Moore. Topics of this series include: donations, recommendations, invitations to events and speaking engagements, employee relations, competitor relations (AT&T, IBM), financial (stock, compensation), FABs, business propositions (investment proposals), environmental topics (dumping, Conservation International), political issues (tax reform, copyright, etc), Strategic Long Range Planning Summary, Intel Corp. products, contributions, questionnaires, Board of Directors, United Way, thank you notes, Intel Museum, Robert Noyce, Caltech correspondence (as chair), marketing, trip reports, and Intel Foundation (Fellowships).
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 1], January-June 1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 2], July-December 1984 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 3], January-March 1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 4], April-June 1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 5], July-September 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 82, Folder 6], October-December 1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 83, Folder 1], January-March 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 83, Folder 2], April-June 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 83, Folder 3], July-September 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 83, Folder 4], October-December 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Incoming Correspondence to Gordon E. Moore (thank you notes) [Originally in Box 83, Folder 5], 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 83, Folder 6], April-June 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence (Robert Noyce Correspondence) [Originally in Box 84, Folder 1], July-September 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 84, Folder 3], January-March 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 84, Folder 4], April-June 1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 84, Folder 5], July-August 1989 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 84, Folder 6], September-December 1989 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 85, Folder 1], January-April 1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 85, Folder 2], May-June 1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 85, Folder 3], July-August 1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 85, Folder 5], October-December 1990 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 86, Folder 1], January-April 1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 86, Folder 2], May-June 1991 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 86, Folder 3], July-August 1991 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 86, Folder 4], September-October 1991 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 86, Folder 5], November-December 1991 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 87, Folder 1], March-April 1992 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 87, Folder 2], May-August 1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Booklet re: Intel Corp. Information Security Policies for Managers [Originally in Box 87, Folder 5], 1992 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Intel Corp. Miscellaneous Correspondence re: Board of Directors, SEC Form - 10K Annual Report 1984, 11th Annual Study [Originally in Box 88, Folder 1], 1983-1993 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Intel Corp. Brochures, Research paper, Outgoing Business Correspondence from Gordon E. Moore [Originally in Box 88, Folder 3], January-May 1993 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 88, Folder 4], June-August 1993 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 88, Folder 5], September-December 1993 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Intel Corp. Miscellaneous Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings [Originally in Box 89, Folder 1], January-April 1993 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Intel Corp. Miscellaneous Correspondence [Originally in Box 89, Folder 2], May-December 1993 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Intel Corp. Miscellaneous Correspondence re: Government Affairs, Congratulatory Letters [Originally in Box 89, Folder 3], 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence, Memorandums [Originally in Box 89, Folder 4], January-April 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 89, Folder 5], May-June 1994 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 89, Folder 6], July-August 1994 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 90, Folder 1], September-October 1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 90, Folder 2], November-December 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence, Annual Reports for Conservation International 1993 [Originally in Box 90, Folder 3], January-February 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 90, Folder 5], May-June 1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 91, Folder 1], July-August 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 91, Folder 2], September-October 1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 91, Folder 3], November-December 1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 91, Folder 5], January-February 1996 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 91, Folder 6], March-April 1996 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 92, Folder 1], May-June 1996 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 92, Folder 2], July-August 1996 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 92, Folder 3], September-December 1996 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 92, Folder 4], January-April 1997 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 93, Folder 1], May-July 1997 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 93, Folder 2], August-December 1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 93, Folder 3], January-July, December 1998 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Restricted until 2019] [Originally in Box 93, Folder 4], February-April 1999 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Restricted until 2020] [Originally in Box 93, Folder 5], November-December 2000 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence, CD re: Carver Mead Nomination [Originally in Box 93, Folder 6], 2001 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence, CD re: Carver Mead Nomination [Restricted until 2021] [Removed from Box 35 Folder 4] [Originally in Box 93, Folder 6], 2001 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Originally in Box 93, Folder 7], 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Outgoing Business Correspondence [Restricted until 2023] [Removed from Box 35 Folder 5] [Originally in Box 93, Folder 7], 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series III: Intel Corporation Financial Reports, 1971-1995
    This subseries consists of financial binders from Intel Corporation, and were found separated among the chronological series. The binders were removed, and materials were placed in acid-free folders. The series is comprised of annual/quarterly reports, financial data, graphs, charts, financial statements, spreadsheets, expense summaries, semiconductor industry statistics, market information, and corporate overviews.
    - Intel Corp. Annual Reports Binder [Originally in Box 173], 1971-1979 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Reports Binder [Originally in Box 173], 1980-1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Annual and Quarterly Reports Binder, SEC Form 10-K [Originally in Box 101, Folder 1], 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Annual and Quarterly Reports, SEC Form 10-Q, News Releases, Stock Participation Plan [Originally in Box 103, Folder 4], 1992-1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series IV: Calendars, 1974-1999
    In this series are 44 calendar planners used by Moore and his secretary. Some calendars contained Moore’s daily schedule while others had only a few events penciled in. Correspondence and agendas were found in three calendars.
    - Executive Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 1], 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Executive Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 2], 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Executive Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 3], 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Executive Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 4], 1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Executive Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 5], 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Bowne Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 6], 1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reminder Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 7], 1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - The 1979 Fortune Diary [Originally in Box 105, Folder 8] (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - The 1980 Fortune Diary [Originally in Box 105, Folder 9] (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Planner [Originally in Box 105, Folder 10], 1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)